

CONTACT

🚹 Ümraniye, İstanbul, Türkiye

☑ 1melike2@gmail.com

05319258027

\* 01.01.1997

/melike-aslan

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

JAVA, C#, Asp.Net MVC, Core Asp.Net MVC, Core Web Api (RESTful Service) Microsoft SQL Server GIT (Version Control System) Object-Oriented Programming Solid Principles Multi Layered Architecture Ado.Net **Entity Framework** HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap Razor Pages

#### LANGUAGES

English B2

# REFERENCES

Dr. Öğr. Üyesi Ebubekir Koç (Manager of Aluteam) Tel: 0532 311 83 19 Email: ekoc@fsm.edu.tr

Bülent Gür

(Manager of Network Akademi)

Tel: 05332679033

Email: bulent\_gur@hotmail.com

# MELİKE ASLAN

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT**

I graduated from Istanbul Fatih Sultan Mehmet Vakıf University in September 2021. I enjoyed studying engineering because of I am a person that interested in technological developments and innovative ideas. I aimed to raise myself as a qualified and versatile engineer with my projects and internship experiences during my undergraduate education. I have gained experience in basic subjects such as working as a team, having self-motivation and doing research. As you can see in my resume, I prepared myself for business life with different trainings and individual researches.At the same time, I was interested in software with the programming lessons. After graduating, I decided to specialize in Software Science. I feel really empowered and confident about software development with the Bootcamps I attended and the Web Programming Course (İşkur-NBUY Program) I completed at Kadıköy Network Academy.



github link: /melikeAslanl

#### **EDUCATION**

BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING | BACHELOR DEGREE

İstanbul Fatih Sultan Mehmet Vakıf University (Full Scholarship) | 2016 -2021

#### INTERNSHIP

Bezmialem Vakıf University Hospital | July 2019 - September 2019

FSMVU BETAM (Biyomedikal Eğitim Tasarım ve Araştırma Merkezi) | July -September 2020 (Smart watch project development with a group of 4 people.) (Detail)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

BACK END DEVELOPER / Hyperdev Technology | July 2022

MATH INSTRUCTOR / Atabey Education Institutes | January 2022 - April 2022

ROBOTIC CODING INSTRUCTOR / Türkiye Teknoloji Takımı Vakfı (T3 Vakfı) | September 2018 - February 2019 (Detail

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

STUDENT ASSISTANT / Fatih Sultan Mehmet Vakıf University ALUTEAM (Alüminyum Test Eğitim ve Araştırma Merkezi) | July- September 2018 (Detail)

# **PROJECTS**

Vehicles Project (Asp.Net MVC Core Web Api - Rest-ful Service) | Haziran 2022 (Code)

Academy Student Management System Project (Asp.Net MVC Core) | May 2022 (Code)

E-Commerce Web Application (Asp.Net MVC Entity Framework Code First) | April 2022 (Code)

GRADUATION PROJECT "GÖZ HAREKETLERİNE DAYALI ARAYÜZ TASARIMINA YARDIMCI SINIFLANDIRMA MODÜLÜ" | 2021 (Detail)

IOT (Internet of Things) PROJECT. Sakarya University | August 2021 (Detail)

# **COURSES AND CERTIFICATES**

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate | July 2022

Web and Mobile Programming Network Academy (İŞKUR) January - June 2022 C# .NET(Web Api) Bootcamp | kodluyoruz.org Online Platform March - June 2022

Kodla Kariyerine Başla-Java kodluyoruz.org Online Platform | Februay 2022 Java Bootcamp | yazilimkoyu.org Online Platform. September - November 2021 Fatih Sultan Mehmet Vakıf University English Preparatory Program Certificate (B2 English Level) (2017) For Certificates papers click here.